<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Password Protector</string>
    <string name="hello_password_protector">Welcome to Password Protector!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_next">NextActivity</string>
    <string name="create">Create Password Data</string>
    <string name="modify">Modify/Delete Password Data</string>

    <color name="grey">#3bcacaca</color>

    <string name="info">So how does this work?\nThe first time you activate this application, you will be
        prompted to input your email address (not so private) AND you will be asked to create a private
        security question AND answer.  It is up to you to decide what that question is, and what the answer is.
        Both the question and answer are case-insensitive, so don\'t worry about caps.
        However it IS sensitive to numbers, punctuation and special characters.  Note that spaces are ignored.
        \nI could just throw the usual security questions at you, but with social media being what it is,
        that info can be hacked by the bad guys.  However if you are required to come up with the question AND answer, it
        is next to impossible for the bad guys to guess both.\nYour email address, and the results of your Q&amp;A are encrypted (AES128) and stored on your phone,
        so you will not be asked for this info again UNLESS you: delete the app from your phone; delete the stored data;
        buy a new phone and download this app again.  At that point you MUST enter the same email (not so hard) AND the
        EXACT same question and answer.  I am asking you to remember that much.  If you forget that EXACT question and answer,
        your data is forever encrypted.  I cannot help you, the NSA cannot help you, even the script kiddie in Eastern Bulgaria
        cannot help you.  If I get granted unlimited access to the newest quantum computers, I might be able to recover your data, but don\'t count on it.\n\n</string>
    <string name="title_activity_read_password">ReadPasswordActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_create">CreateActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_read">ReadActivity</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="title_activity_update">UpdateActivity</string>

</resources>
